[music]
>> I'm like kind of freaking out right now.
In T-minus 4 hours, I'm surprising my
boyfriend at the 5 Seconds of Summer
concert and I'm taking y'all with me.
Okay, it is now time to find our train.
Ah, so cute.
And a fan made dolls of us and he was
showing me like me and
It's really cute. We're on the train.
It's going to be a long ass train ride.
I'm like so excited that I don't think I
can
I should I looked up to meet a tall boy
with soft green eyes and curly locks
covering his face. Her eyes met for a
split second and I saw him blush a
little.
>> I should blush.
>> Is it bad?
>> No, it's great.
>> Guys, there's a girl who's watching one
of my YouTube videos on the train right
now. I'm being so for real.
Wait, that's like literally me. Guys, we
just got here.
This is our spot, right? No, I'm
actually freaking out.
Ooh.
Dude, this looks like San Antonio.
Do you want to be in a fit check?
5 Seconds of Summer
Are you excited?
>> I'm so excited.
>> Guys, I don't know why I feel like I'm
going to throw up right now. Wait.
>> Um
>> This is a tutorial for
>> [music]
>> the dance that we're trying to learn.
This is easy, we can do this.
Dude, there's literally like people up
>> They're on the bridge.
>> the hill.
>> Oh my god, they're walking down
>> Like this is insane.
>> Oh.
>> Wait, [screaming] wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
What time is it?
We're about to see the most legendary
opener of all time.
They're barking at him.
>> I can't if I'm doing the dance right
here in FRONT OF EVERYONE.
>> [music]
>> WHAT?
>> YEAH.
>> [music]
>> SO LONG, SO GOOD.
SO LONG,
SO GOOD.
>> [music]
[music]
>> WHAT?
>> [music]
>> YEAH.